

Contact

SydneyKBouchard@gmail.com (802) 598-7792

Education

Bloc

User Experience Design Program September 2018 - February 2019

Bentley University

BS Marketing BS Media Arts May 2014

Skills

UX Research Prototyping
Wireframing User Testing
Branding User Research
Visual Design Info Architecture
Photography

Tools

Sketch

Figma

InVision

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

jQuery

GitHub

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Final Cut Pro

Summary

I am a Philadelphia based designer building on my creative marketing and media background to create inventive, user-friendly experiences.

Recent Design Projects

Keeps | Collaborative Cloud Storage

Designed as a more approachable and user-friendly answer to cloud storage. Created through user research and visual design, utilizing Figma, Sketch, InVision, and Adobe Photoshop.

BusyBus | Public Transportation Application

Created to be an effective and simple solution to public transit issues in major cities. Utilized User research, visual design and front end development.

Work Experience

Dick's Last Resort - Boston, MA

Marketing Director, August 2016 - August 2018

- Design all brand advertisements, promotions, and store signage
- Create unique marketing and branding initiatives to drive sales
- Create and share content for the DLR Social Networks

Fishers Island Lemonade - Boston MA

Marketing and Sales Manager, January 2016 - July 2016

- Design and create all advertising and promotional material
- Work with our distributors to acquire new accounts
- Create and share content for all of our social media platforms

Saxtons River Distillery - Brattleboro, VT

Marketing Director, August 2014 - January 2016

- Create and maintain the Saxtons River Distillery website
- Create all print and advertising material
- Responsible for a 108% national market sales increase in my first year
- Create and maintain all social media pages